

## **BENJAMIN ABITBOL**

## **CONTACT**

6

055 66 80 262



benjiab@hotmail.com



Netanya, Israel

## **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

- Front-End Development
- QA Automation Testing
- Software Testing
- Network Security
- Networks & Systems Security
- Network Architecture
- Digital Marketing

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML

**CSS** 

JavaScript

React

Angular

**REST** 

**MERN** 

**MEAN** 

Jira

Linux

Windows

Git

Wordpress

## LANGUAGES SPOKEN

French: Native English: Fluent Hebrew: Advanced

## **EXTRA-ACTIVITIES**

- Crypto and Blockchain
- Advisor for Blockchain Decentralized Projects

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a self-taught Web Developer. I have experience developing full-stack applications (MVC architecture, API) following best practices (refactoring, code standards). I have deep foundations in JavaScript.

I am a self-teaching individual at the core, passionate, motivated and dedicated to coding.

I worked as a QA in an automation testing team at Checkpoint (System automation testing framework) and took a 3 months' intensive course to study JavaScript and the MEAN/MERN stack to kick-start my career.

## **PROJECTS**

built using React/MERN Stack built using Wordpress built using Node, Angularis and MongoDB built using JS/HTML/CSS IoP-Connect
BababoxTV
The Home Cook
My Portfolio

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## Checkpoint, Tel Aviv Automation Testing Team | 2017-2018

**Duties and Responsibilities** 

- Performing daily Automation Testing on System (framework based on Java)
- Maintain, expand, and improve our automated testing framework
- Work with Automation team to triage and identify bugs, collaborate with development team to develop comprehensive testing plan
- Stay up-to-date with new testing tools and test strategies (Kibana) and improve results
- Extensive use of Jira management tool to report and track bugs.
- CCSA/CCSE certifications
- Extensive use of Linux command line

### **Elevation Academy, Tel Aviv**

Coding Bootcamp | Apr, 2017 - Jun, 2017

**Duties and Responsibilities** 

- Led two Hackathons teams building projects using MEAN stack
- Developed freelance projects: building landing pages from PSD to html/css/javascript (mobile responsive)
- Deep Foundations in JavaScript.

## Advisers Web Agency, Paris Web Developer | 2016-2017

**Duties and Responsibilities** 

- Web development for responsive websites (HTML/CSS/JS)
- Troubleshooted issues affecting production
- Collaborating and co-developing with Application UI/UX Designer

# Digital Marketing Career Digital Marketing Manager at Deloitte, Bill Tornade and Gigaspaces Technologies | 2014 –2016

**Duties and Responsibilities** 

- Organization of events on the French Territory
- Leading Facebook and LinkedIn ads campaigns SEO and SEM Optimization
- Extensive use of automation tools (Salesforce, Sales Genius, Rainking...)

## **EDUCATION**

2017 2007-2012

2007

Intensive Coding Bootcamp – Elevation Academy

Master Degree with honours – Business School – ISG Paris Bachelors of Science – Physics with honours – College Yabne Paris